<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Machine Unlearning on Àlex</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/machine-unlearning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Machine Unlearning on Àlex</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 12:20:47 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/machine-unlearning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes on SSSE: Efficiently Erasing Samples From Trained Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/papers/ssse-efficiently-erasing-samples-from-trained-machine-learning-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 12:20:47 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/papers/ssse-efficiently-erasing-samples-from-trained-machine-learning-models/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is part of my notes on AI research papers. I do this to learn and communicate what I understand. Feel free to comment if you have any suggestion, that would be very much appreciated.&#xA;The following post is a comment on the paper SSSE: Efficiently Erasing Samples From Trained Machine Learning Models by Alexandra Peste, Dan Alistarh, and Christoph H. Lampert.&#xA;Peste et. al. propose Single-Step Sample Erasure (SSSE), a method to efficiently and effectively erase samples from trained machine learning models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Mixed-Privacy Forgetting in Deep Networks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/papers/mixed-privacy-forgetting-in-deep-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 10:13:13 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/papers/mixed-privacy-forgetting-in-deep-networks/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is part of my notes on AI research papers. I do this to learn and communicate what I understand. Feel free to comment if you have any suggestion, that would be very much appreciated.&#xA;The following post is a comment on the paper Mixed-Privacy Forgetting in Deep Networks by Aditya Golatkar, Alessandro Achille, Avinash Ravichandran, Marzia Polito, and Stefano Soatto.&#xA;Golatkar et. al. introduce a novel method for forgetting in a mixed-privacy setting, where a core subset of the training samples will not be forgotten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Multi Class Explainable Unlearning for Image Classification via Weight Filtering</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/papers/multi-class-explainable-unlearning-for-image-classification-via-weight-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:36:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/papers/multi-class-explainable-unlearning-for-image-classification-via-weight-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is part of my notes on AI research papers. I do this to learn and communicate what I understand. Feel free to comment if you have any suggestion, that would be very much appreciated.&#xA;The following post is a comment on the paper Multi Class Explainable Unlearning for Image Classification via Weight Filtering by Samuele Poppi, Sara Sarto, Marcella Cornia, Lorenzo Baraldi and Rita Cucchiara.&#xA;Samuele P., et. al.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
